In this exercise, we're gonna learn more about buttons and forms.
在这个练习里 我们会学习更多的 按钮与表格的相关知识
We're going to learn how to add buttons to your website,
我们将会学习如何在我们的网站中 加入各种按钮
how to style them using the button classes that are available in.
以及如何利用 Bootstrap 的按钮类 来定制这些按钮
We'll also learn about and how we create and style the elements.
我们同样会学习如何创建表格
Using classes.
以及如何用 Bootstrap 类来定制它
To get started download the contactus.html file that we have provided for
为此 你需要先下载我们提供给你的 一个 contactus.html 文件
you and then move it to the Con Fusion folder.
然后将它移到 conFusion 文件夹里
Now this file we are going to integrate it into our website.
我们将把这个文件 整合进我们的网站中
So when you open the webpage in a browser,
如果你用浏览器打开这个文件的话
this is what it is going to look like, in the browser.
它应该会长成这样
So you can see that on the webpage we have
你可以看到它已经有了
the web page already partially styled by us, with some information.
一部分信息
Now within this web page, you're going to add some buttons, and
然后在这个网页中 你将要加进一些按钮
also add in a form for the user to submit feedback
和一个拿来让用户提交反馈
to their restaurant.
的表格
Before we get started adding forms and
不过在此之前
buttons, let's first integrate this web page into our website.
还是先把这个网页 整合进我们的网站吧
So this means that we have to go into the nav bar and then set up all the links
为此 我们要在我们的导航栏中
correctly in the nav bar, not only for contactus.html page, but
加进一些合适的链接 以将我们做过的所有网页整合在一起
also the previous two pages, index.html and aboutus.html.
不仅是现在这个 contactus.html 还有之前的 index.html 和 aboutus.html
So you all know how to do this, so go and edit the nav bars on these three pages.
我想你应该知道怎么做 所以现在就去把这些链接加好吧
And update the links there, so that you can move from any page to
当你实现好之后 你就能通过导航栏
any other page by just clicking the links on the nav bars.
从任一网页跳转到任一网页了
In addition, while you are at it, add two new glyphicons,
特别的 我们还要 加进两个 glyphicon 图标
and icon to the Nav bar.
和一个 Font Awesome 图标
One for the Menu item and one for the Contact Us item.
一个是为了装点 Menu 那个链接 另一个则是为了 Contact 那个链接
So we'll be using a glyph icon for the Menu item and will use another
也就是说我们要 在 Menu 链接处用 glyphicons
Font Awesome icon for the contact link in our nav bar.
以及在 Contact 链接处用 Font Awesome
So as specified in the instructions,
接下来让我们跟从指示
let's update these nav bars and come back and look at the result.
来更新我们的导航栏吧
Taking a look at the contactus.html page,
进到 contactus.html 的代码部分
let me quickly review how I added the two icons into the navbar.
让我们来看看是怎样在 导航栏中加进图标的
For the menu item,
对于 Menu 链接
you can see that I am using a glyphicon-list-alt for the menu item.
你可以看到我用了一个 glyphicon-list-alt 图标
And for the contact item, I am using a Font Awesome,
然后对 Contact 链接 我用了一个 Font Awesome 中的
Font Awesome envelope icon for the contact links there.
fa-envelope-o 图标
Our next step is to add a button bar to the contactus.html page.
我们下一步要做的就是在 contactus.html 中 加进一个按钮栏了
Now when you go into the page, you will see that we have identified
你可以看到我已经在这里
the location where the button group is going to be added.
表明了应该在哪里加进我们的按钮
So go into that location and then we'll replace this
所以让我们用相应的代码
line there with the code for the button groups.
把这行字替换掉吧
After replacing the code, let's quickly review what this new code does here.
当我们加好代码后 让我们来看看 这段代码是什么意思
So you can see that in this new code,
你可以看到我在按钮组部分的最外层 用的是一个定义了
I have defined a div with a class called btn-group.
class="btn-group" 的 div
So this contains a group of buttons.
这意味着其下将会有一组按钮
I have three buttons in here, and I am using the a tag to define the button so
在这个栗子里 我用设置了 type="button" 的 a 标签
I am saying a type button, and for
来实现了三个按钮
the class I am using button button primary for one of the buttons.
同时 我还设置了一些类 比如说对第一个按钮 我就设置了
This button is a button to make a phone call to the restaurant.
class="btn btn-primary" 这个按钮允许用户通过它来给我们打电话
So, that's why for the H graph I am specifying it as it telephone and
这也是为什么我对其 href 属性 设置了 href="tel:+xxx"
the phone number of the restaurant.
其中 xxx 正是我们餐厅的电话号码
The second button is for Skype.
对第二个按钮 则连接到了 Skype
So I have included, again, Skype button here,
你可以看到我将其内容设为了 Skype
and also included a Font Awesome icon for Skype there.
以及 Font Awesome 图标 用的野兽 fa-skype
The third button is for sending emails.
第三个按钮则用作发电子邮件
So I have updated the A tag, with the btn btn-success, and then the href,
所以你可以看到我对其 href 属性 设置了 href="mailto:xxx"
I am setting it to the mail ID of the restaurant.
其中 xxx 正是我们餐厅的电子邮箱地址
Of course, remember that this is a fake mail ID, so
当然了 这个邮箱地址是我瞎编的
don't try to send mail to that ID.
所以不要尝试对其发邮件...
And also, I added an envelope icon to the email.
你还可以看到我在这里用了一个 Font Awesome 的 fa-envelope-o 图标
So after making this changes, let's go and review our webpage.
当我们做完这些改动后 让我们回去看看我们的网页吧
Returning to our webpage, you would notice that now the,
来到浏览器这里 你可以看到
Nav bar has been updated with icons for all the links in the nav bar.
我们的导航栏已经更新完毕了
Second point to note is the addition of the three
而且在这里多了三个
buttons, in a button bar, to the contents of the website.
很好看的按钮
So now you can see that I have three buttons here, call, Skype, and email.
分别是 Call, Skype 和 Email
Now, this blue outline here is because I am using brackets.
注意 这个浅蓝色方框 是 Brackets 这个软件的功能
So whenever I am editing any code in brackets,
它代表着我当前在 Brackets 中
you will see the blue line appear there.
选中的代码所对应的部分
So let me just turn that off so that's it's more clear to you.
为使你更专注于页面本身
So let's take a look at the button bar.
我打算把这个功能关掉
So you can see that in the button bar now I have three buttons here.
现在你应该能更清晰地
The Call button, the Skype button, and the Email button.
看到我们加的这三个按钮 以及它们和周围元素之间的位置关系
So if we click on any one of these then the appropriate function will be started.
如果我们点击其中一个按钮的话 相应的功能就应该被唤起
In our next set of step, we're going to add the form
下一步我们要做的
element to the contactus.html webpage.
就是在这里加进一个表格
So here where it says form goes here, I'm going to create a feedback form
你也可以在这看到一行小字 告诉你"表格放这里"
that the visitors can used to send feedback to the restaurant.
所以我们将在这放一个用户能用于 向我们反馈意见的表格
Of course at the end of this exercise this form will not work at the moment because
当然了 即使是在本练习的最后 该表格也不会有实际的这种功能
we don't have the server side setup to receive the information from the form, but
因为那需要服务端的支持
in the later courses they will activate this
所以我们将会在后续课程中
form to be able to submit information to the restaurant.
把这个表格的功能彻底实现
Returning to our web page.
回到我们的网页
In brackets, I'm going to replace this form goes here with
我们要将表格的代码
a set of code in order to create a simple form.
替换掉这行"Form goes here" 【注 是"表格放这里"的意思】
I have now substituted the form code in place.
你可以看到我现在把代码贴好了
In the HTML code let's quickly review the new code that we have added,
接下来就让我们看看 这段代码是怎样的
so you can see that I have added a form tag here, and
你可以看到我在主体部分的最外层 用了一个 HTML 的 form 标签
with a class horizontal, which means that there are items in this form will be layed
我还对其设置了 class="form-horizontal" 意味着该表格中的元素
out in the horizontal manner, so we have already seen the form horizontal class for
将会是"水平排列"的 事实上在我们第一次
our bootstrap, when we debuted forms in bootstrap.
学习 Bootstrap 中的表格时 就已经见过类似的类了
Inside that form class, I have two form-groups here.
然后再其下 我用了两个 div 并对它们设置了 class="form-group"
The first form-group is used to create the entry for the first name.
我将第一个 div 实现成了 让用户输入名字的输入框
The second form group is to create the entry point for the last name here.
第二个则实现成了输入姓的
So after making these changes let's go and look at the result.
做了这些改变后 让我们看看 我们的网页有哪些变化吧
So you can now notice that on the webpage we now have two fields
你可以看到在我们的网页上 出现了两个输入框
that have been created for entering the first name and the last name of the users.
用户可以通过它们来输入 他们的姓和名
Pertaining to the HTML code, let me just remind you again that the form group
对了 有一点要说一下 这里这个 form-group 类
class automatically adds the row features to that diff.
会自动给这个 div 加上 Bootstrap 里面的 row 的特性
So inside that, whatever contents we have,
所以在我们可以对其下的元素
we can now apply column classes to that content.
设置各种 col 属性
So that's why you see me applying col-sm-2 to the label and
正因如此 你可以看到 我对那个 label 设置了 col-sm-2
col-sm-10 to the div in here.
而对那个 div 设置了 col-sm-10
So this is a nested set of columns for this row.
如果你对 Bootstrap 网格系统 掌握得不错
This is nested inside another column which is in the webpage itself.
那么你应该就能清晰地认辨出 这里的层次结构
Our next iteration to the HTML code for the farm is to create
我们下一步要做的
the input group for entering the telephone number.
是加进一个能让用户 输入他们电话号码的东西
Now when I clear the info group for the telephone number.
你可以看到我用了许多 以前没用过的新元素
You would see that I'm using the form group.
不过最外层仍然是一个设置了 class="form-group" 的 div
Now, inside the form group I'm using an input-group here in the code.
然后在其下 我用了一个设置了 class="input-group" 的 div
This input-group contains an input
然后在其中 我用了两个设置了 class="input-group-addon" 的 div
group add on which allows me to add the left parentheses,
分别代表着左括号和右括号
and another input group add on that allows me to add the right parenthesis
然后它们之间 就是让用户输入 电话地区号的地方了
to that particular input element there.
事实上如果你对美国电话号码
So this input element I am using it to allow the user to enter the area code.
的表现方式比较熟悉的话
So if you're familiar with the US phone number representations
你大概就知道一般而言
you will see that the area code is always enclosed inside parentheses.
电话地区号都是填在一对括号之间的
So this allows me to add add ons
所以为了实现这种演出效果
to the input elements there.
我用了 input-group-addon 这个类
Now in addition I have added in one more field for
接下来 我还实现了一个
allowing the user to enter their email.
用户用于填写他们 电子邮箱地址的地方
So if this is the email ID field here, the label, and the input there.
你可以看到我写了相应的一些代码
So after making these changes, let's go and have a look at the page.
做完这些改变之后 让我们看看 我们的网页现在长啥样吧
Now in the webpage, you see that we now have the contact telephone
你可以看到我们多了几个输入框
number, which can be specified as an area code within
这里这个允许用户输入电话地区号
parenthesis, and the telephone number next to it.
跟它挨着的这个输入框 则允许用户输入电话号码
The email can be entered in the email field.
在它们下面这个输入框 则是 让用户输入他们的邮箱地址的
Our next addition to the font is a check box,
我们接下来要实现的是选择框
which allows the user to specify whether they want to be contacted or not.
它能让用户选择他们 是否愿意被联系
In addition, I am using a select element in order to let the users
我还会实现一个下拉菜单 来让用户选择他们愿意被联系的方式
specify whether they want to be contacted by telephone or by email.
比如 电话还是电子邮件
So, adding these two.
然后我在这贴好了代码
Looking at the code, you see that I have a form-group here which encloses that.
你可以看到这两部分的最外层 仍然是设置了 class="form-group" 的 div
And inside of that I am defining a div with a check box in here.
于其一 我在其下放了一个设置了 class="checkbox" 的 div
And I have an input type check box in there.
然后在其中 我用了一个设置了 type="checkbox" 的 input
And then correspondingly,
相对应的 其后跟着一行字
the message there saying, may we contact you?
"May we contact you" 【"我们能联系你吗"】
Question mark.
问号
So if the user checks the check box,
如果用户选中了这个选择框
then the user is indicating that they could be contacted.
就意味着该用户 不抗拒我们联系 ta
So that is enclosed inside this check box in here.
接下来要做的
Now below that, I have a select element there.
就是实现一个下拉菜单了
For the select element I have two options.
你可以看到这个下拉菜单有两个选项
Telephone and email.
Tel. 和 Email 【电话 和 电子邮件】
After making these changes, let's go back and look at our webpage.
做完这些改动后
Now before we go, let me show you how we have styled these elements here,
让我们看看我们的网页 有什么变化吧
and how we have specified the column classes.
不过在此之前 我还想提醒你们注意 我在这里定制这些元素的方式
Now, as you recall, the form group already provides the row class for us.
特别要注意的是 form-group 是 自带 row 属性的 所以在其下
So inside there, the checkbox div,
我直接用了 col 相关的类 来定制这些元素
I have given it appropriate column specification there.
我给我的选择框和下拉菜单
And then also, the select
都定义了相关的 col 属性
element I have given the appropriate column specification there.
这里也算是对 Bootstrap 网格系统的
So I want you to make specific note of this information in the coach.
一个复习与应用吧
Now let's go and look at the page.
现在让我们去看看我们的网页
Now you see that in the web page,
你可以看到
we now have a check box which we can check on or off.
我们这里有一个选择框
And then the message there, and also this selector element which allows us to
在其后跟着一行字
specify whether we want to be contacted by telephone or email.
和一个下拉菜单
The next element what we are adding to the form is a textarea.
接下来我们要实现的 是一个多行文本输入框
This is the place where the user can type in.
这将是用户
They're comics.
输入他们的评论的地方
So here I am using another form-group for that.
你可以看到我在其最外层 用的仍然是 form-group
And inside that form-group, I have a label to specify the information.
然后在其中 我用了一个 label 来向用户说明这个输入框是干啥的
And then I am using another dev, which in close text area
接着就是多行文本框本身了 我用了一个 div 来封装它
whose values are set to be 12 rows there so
并且对其本身 我设置了 row="12"
the text area will allow the user to input 12 rows of text in there.
这意味着这个多行文本框有 12 行
So with these changes, again going back to our webpage,
做完这些改变后 让我们回去看看 我们的网页变成咋样了
this is the next result of adding the text area to our webpage.
你可以看到在我们的网页里
So now you see that your feedback page is
多出了一个很大的输入框
already taking very well.
而且整个表格看上去也很棒
Our last addition to the form is the submit button.
我们最后要实现的 就是一个用于提交的按钮了
So here I am creating a submit button by using the button and
在这我用了一个设置了 type="submit" 的 button 标签
specifying its type as submit.
来实现这个提交按钮
I specify the classes btn btn-primary and then specify that
我同时还对其设置了 class="btn btn-primary"
the contents inside the button that should be displayed the text inside the button.
然后对其内容 我设置了 "Send Feedback"
And also, I specified for the dev.
注意到我用了一个 div 来封装该按钮 我对这个 div 设置了合适的类
I used the classes to appropriately position the button in the.
从而能将这个按钮放在合适的位置
With these changes, let's go and have one final look at our webpage.
做完这些后 让我们最后瞅一眼 我们的网页吧
Going back to our webpage, we now see that the form is now complete.
来到我们的网页 你可以看到 我们的这个表格已经完整了
So you can see that you have all the various fields in the form.
你可以看到很多输入框
And also we have specified the button
同时还有一个按钮
which the user clicks in order to submit the form information.
用户可以通过点击它 来提交他所输入的东西
Now, taking one final look at our web page, in this exercise
让我们回顾一下 我们在这个练习里干了什么吧
we have added a new page called contact us to HTML to our website.
我们在我们的网站中加进了 一个叫 contactus.html 的文件
We styled the nav bar
我们把导航栏定制好了
specifying icons for all the links in the nav bar.
并且在其中加了一些小图标
Then we added the button bar here that allows users
我们在页尾这里加进了一个按钮栏
to either call, Skype or email the company.
它允许用户向我们打电话 发电子邮件或者发 Skype 邀请
And finally we added a form for
然后最后我们还加进了一个表格
the users to send back comments to the restaurant.
从而用户能够通过它来提交反馈
And we used various form elements, and Bootstrap's classes,
我们用了若干 Bootstrap 的类
in order to style the form appropriately.
来定制这个表格
This completes this exercise.
以上 我们完成了这次练习